ACCION International Records MS196
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Communications and External Affairs records, 1950 -- 2012; 1985 -- 2005; MS196.006; 62.7 Linear Feet; 238 Audiovisual Object(s); 365 Digital Object(s)
  - Reprints and publicity, 1960 -- 2011; MS196.006.004; 18.1 Linear Feet; 147 Audiovisual Object(s)
    - Chicago Tribune, 2002; MS196.006.004.018.00047; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Filed Clips, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00048; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Filed Clips Media Relations Report 2, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00049; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Online Clips Media Relations Report 2, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00050; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Online Clips, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00051; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Economy 21, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00052; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Tagblatt, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00053; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Latin Trade, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00054; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00055; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Stanford Business, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00056; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - United Press International, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00057; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Boston Business Journal, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00058; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Worth, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00059; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Fast Company Magazine, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00060; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Forbes, 2004; MS196.006.004.018.00061; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - The Financial Times, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00062; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Bank Technology News, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00063; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Chronicle of Philanthropy, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00064; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Micronews, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00065; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Worth, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00066; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Unitarian Universalist World, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00067; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Burrelles Luce Clips A1, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00068; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Burrelles Luce Clips AUSA, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00069; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - New York Times, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00070; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Business Week, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00071; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Associated Press, 2005; MS196.006.004.018.00072; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - ACCION International Press, 1998 -- 2000; MS196.006.004.018.00073; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Microfinance General, 1995 -- 1996; MS196.006.004.018.00074; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Microloan Coverage, 1999; MS196.006.004.018.00075; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Microcredit Articles - General, 1997 -- 1999; MS196.006.004.018.00076; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - Hurricane Mitch, 1998; MS196.006.004.018.00077; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - ADMIC Press Material, 1992 -- 1996; MS196.006.004.018.00078; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - ADMIC, 1995 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.018.00079; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 18)
    - BancoSol, 1989 -- 1997; MS196.006.004.019.00001; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - BancoSol Press Material, 1992 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.019.00002; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Banco Solidario Del Ecuador, 1998; MS196.006.004.019.00003; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Banco Solidario Del Ecuador Press Material, 1999 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.019.00004; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Ban Gente, 1997 -- 1999; MS196.006.004.019.00005; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Ban Gente Press, 1999; MS196.006.004.019.00006; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Compartamos, 1999; MS196.006.004.019.00007; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Compartamos Bond Issue, 2002; MS196.006.004.019.00008; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - CrediAmigo (Banco do Nordeste), 2002; MS196.006.004.019.00009; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Fundacion Emprender, 1992 -- 1997; MS196.006.004.019.00010; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Emprender / Argentina, 1995 -- 1997; MS196.006.004.019.00011; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Emprender / Colombia, 1995 -- 1999; MS196.006.004.019.00012; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Colombia / Emprender Press, 1998; MS196.006.004.019.00013; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - FAMA, 1996 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.019.00014; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - FAMA Press Material, 1993; MS196.006.004.019.00015; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - FAMA Marketing Materials, 2002; MS196.006.004.019.00016; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - El Comercio / Paraguay, 2002; MS196.006.004.019.00017; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - FED Press Material, 1988 -- 1997; MS196.006.004.019.00018; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - FENAPE Press Material, 1995 -- 1997; MS196.006.004.019.00019; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - FENAPE, 1994 -- 1995; MS196.006.004.019.00020; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Finamerica, 1996; MS196.006.004.019.00021; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Finamerica Press Material, 1992 -- 1996; MS196.006.004.019.00022; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - FMSD, 2001; MS196.006.004.019.00023; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Funadeh - Honduras, 1997; MS196.006.004.019.00024; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Funadeh - Honduras Press Material, 1995 -- 1996; MS196.006.004.019.00025; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - FUNDAP / PROSEM, 1996; MS196.006.004.019.00026; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Fundacion Paraguay Press Material, 1990 -- 1995; MS196.006.004.019.00027; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Albert Bildner, 1994; MS196.006.004.019.00028; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Genesis Empresarial, 1997 -- 2000; MS196.006.004.019.00029; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Mibanco, 1995 -- 1998; MS196.006.004.019.00030; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Mibanco, 1997 -- 2003; MS196.006.004.019.00031; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Mibanco Press Materials, 1996 -- 1997; MS196.006.004.019.00032; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Mibanco Press, 1997 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.019.00033; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - Mibanco, 2002; MS196.006.004.019.00034; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - MultiCredit Bank / ACCION Empresarial, 1996; MS196.006.004.019.00035; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 19)
    - MultiCredit Bank Press, 1996; MS196.006.004.020.00001; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - SOGEBANK Press, 2000; MS196.006.004.020.00002; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - SOGEBANK, 1999 -- 2001; MS196.006.004.020.00003; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - UMU, 1997; MS196.006.004.020.00004; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Credife, 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00005; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - CML ( Caribbean MF, ltd), 1999 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.020.00006; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - FUSAI, 2001 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.020.00007; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - FUSAI Press, 2001; MS196.006.004.020.00008; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Real Microcredit (Brazil), 2002; MS196.006.004.020.00009; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Real Microcredit - Press Coverage, 2002; MS196.006.004.020.00010; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION USA - US Programs General Info, 1995 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.020.00011; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION Atlanta - Press, 2001 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.020.00012; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION Atlanta, 2000 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.020.00013; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCON Chicago, 1993 -- 2003; MS196.006.004.020.00014; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION Chicago Press Materials, 1995 -- 2003; MS196.006.004.020.00015; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION New Mexico Press Materials, 1996 -- 2001; MS196.006.004.020.00016; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION New Mexico, 1995 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.020.00017; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Reprints Press Coverage, 1998 -- 1999; MS196.006.004.020.00018; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION New York, 1992 -- 1996; MS196.006.004.020.00019; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION New York Press Material, 1997 -- 2003; MS196.006.004.020.00020; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION San Diego, 1994 -- 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00021; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION San Diego Press Material, 1998 -- 2003; MS196.006.004.020.00022; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION Texas, 1993 -- 1999; MS196.006.004.020.00023; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION Texas Press Material, 1996 -- 2003; MS196.006.004.020.00024; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION USA - Miami, 2002; MS196.006.004.020.00025; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - El Paso Times Editorial / Response, 2001; MS196.006.004.020.00026; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Working Capital Press, 2001; MS196.006.004.020.00027; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - ACCION USA Press, 2000 -- 2003; MS196.006.004.020.00028; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Working Capital General Info, 1998 -- 2002; MS196.006.004.020.00029; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Reprins Major Press Coverage, 1998 -- 2001; MS196.006.004.020.00030; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Client Story - Ricardo Chacon, BancoSol, 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00031; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Client Story - Norma Salazar, Genesis, 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00032; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Lilia Cecilia Chavez - Mibanco, 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00033; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Ana Elvia Tocasuche de Ladino, 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00034; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Georgina Moronto - Client of ACCION New York, 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00035; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Martha Veronica Toledo - FAMA, 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00036; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Elizabeth Baez - Client Story ACCION Chicago, 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00037; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Bertha Sandoval Rivera - Mibanco, 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00038; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - Maria Leonor Garcia -FINSOL, 1998; MS196.006.004.020.00039; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 20)
    - VOA, 1988; MS196.006.004.021.00001; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WBUR - "Con Salsa" Boston, 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00002; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WBUR - "The Connection" Boston, 1995 -- 2000; MS196.006.004.021.00003; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WRKO (Boston), 1989; MS196.006.004.021.00004; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - ABC - BusinessWorld, 1988; MS196.006.004.021.00005; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - ABC - Good Morning America, 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00006; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - ABC - Prime Time Live, 1990 -- 1995; MS196.006.004.021.00007; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - ABC - World News Tonight, 1988 -- 1999; MS196.006.004.021.00008; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Adam Smith's Money World (National Cable), 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00009; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Channel 7 Boston, 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00010; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - CBS News, 1988 -- 1993; MS196.006.004.021.00011; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - 60 Minutes, 2001; MS196.006.004.021.00012; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - CNBC, 2000; MS196.006.004.021.00013; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - CNBC - World Business, 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00014; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - CNN, 1993 -- 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00015; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - CNN en Espanol, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00016; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Community Cable (Boston), 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00017; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 1989 -- 1992; MS196.006.004.021.00018; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Discovery Channel, 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00019; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Dr. Joy Browne Show, 2000; MS196.006.004.021.00020; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Foundation for Global Broadcasting, 1989; MS196.006.004.021.00021; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Koppel Communications, 1989; MS196.006.004.021.00022; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - McNeil Lehrer Newshour, 1990 -- 1996; MS196.006.004.021.00023; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - NBC Nightly News, 1988 -- 1992; MS196.006.004.021.00024; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - NBC - Today Show, 1995 -- 1996; MS196.006.004.021.00025; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - New England Today, 1992; MS196.006.004.021.00026; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WBZ TV "Eyewitness News" Boston, 1988 -- 1999; MS196.006.004.021.00027; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WCVB "Aqui" Boston, 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00028; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WCVB "The Chronicle" Boston, 1989 -- 1996; MS196.006.004.021.00029; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WGBH Boston PBS, 1989 -- 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00030; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Power of Small Change, 1999; MS196.006.004.021.00031; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - ROOY Media, 1992 -- 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00032; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - To Our Credit, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00033; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WGBH - "La Plaza" Boston PBS, 1989; MS196.006.004.021.00034; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WHLL TV 27 Boston, 1992; MS196.006.004.021.00035; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WJLA "Working Woman" (DC), 1996; MS196.006.004.021.00036; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WNBC-TV (New York), 1999; MS196.006.004.021.00037; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WSJ TV, 1994; MS196.006.004.021.00038; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Univision, 1989 -- 1993; MS196.006.004.021.00039; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - WorldNet TV, 1999; MS196.006.004.021.00040; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Northbridge Productions, 2004; MS196.006.004.021.00041; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Pat Summerall Productions, 2004; MS196.006.004.021.00042; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Planet Earth Television, 1989 -- 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00043; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Media Kit #5, 1991; MS196.006.004.021.00044; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Media Kit #4, 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00045; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Media Kit #3, 1990; MS196.006.004.021.00046; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Media Kit #2, 1989; MS196.006.004.021.00047; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Media Kit Pieces, 1989; MS196.006.004.021.00048; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Media Kit #1, 1989; MS196.006.004.021.00049; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Denver Post, 1987 -- 1991; MS196.006.004.021.00050; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 1999; MS196.006.004.021.00051; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Nueva Economia, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00052; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - New York, NY News - Brooklyn, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00053; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Que Onda Houston Texas Ed., 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00054; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Latin Finance, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00055; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - New Mex Busi Albuquerque NM, Albuquerque Journal, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00056; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Ultima Hora "Economia " Asuncion, Paraguay, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00057; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Chicago IL, Extra- South Side, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00058; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Diego Navy Dispatch At Ease, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00059; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Paso Times, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00060; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Chicago IL La Raza, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00061; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Californian, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00062; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Albuquerque NM Journal, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00063; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - The American Benefactor Summer, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00064; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Nicavance, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00065; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Hoy Dinero Ecuador, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00066; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - McAllen, TX El Periodico, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00067; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Sacramento, CA El Hispano, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00068; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Paso Times, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00069; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Diario Economia, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00070; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Denton, TX Record-Chronicle, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00071; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Monday Developments, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00072; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Paso, TX Times, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00073; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - La Prensa Nicaragua, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00074; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Antonio Texas Express News Morning Edition, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00075; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Chicago, IL Tribute, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00076; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Paso Times, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00077; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - PMP Forum Spring / Summer, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00078; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Comercio, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00079; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Sol De San Diego, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00080; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Antonio Business Journal, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00081; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - DRCLAS News Winter, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00082; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Community Investment News from the Calvert Foundation, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00083; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Albuquerque Journal, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00084; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Hope, SRI, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00085; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - New Mexico Business Journal, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00086; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Valley Morning Star, Harlinger TX, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00087; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - The Monitor, McAllen Tex, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00088; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - McAllen Monitor, Brownsville Herald, El Heraldo, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00089; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Paso BZ Times, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00090; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Chicago, IL Extra Suburban South North Editions, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00091; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Paso Times, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00092; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - New Mexico Business Weekly, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00093; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - La Presa, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00094; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Antonio Business Journal, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00095; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Antonio Express-News, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00096; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Women's City Club, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00097; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - St. Paul, NM, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00098; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Non Profit Times, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00099; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Antonio Business Journal, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00100; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Antonio Business Journal, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00101; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Paso Times, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00102; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - St. Paul, NM, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00103; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Antonio Business Journal, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00104; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Grameen Dialogue, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00105; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Antonio Express-News, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00106; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - News & Views, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00107; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Paso Times, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00108; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Crain's Chicago Bz, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00109; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Vista, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00110; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Antonio Business Journal, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00111; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - San Antonio Express-News, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00112; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Soroptimist, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00113; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Albuquerque NM Journal, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00114; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Boston Business Journal, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00115; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)